psiphontoday.com 2016-12-11

# Psiphon Today

## Privacy Policy for Psiphon Today

Psiphon is committed to protecting the privacy interests of its customers, end users, distributors and suppliers. This privacy policy is intended to provide you with general information on how your personal information may be used. Psiphon is a Canadian corporation with its head office located in Ontario, and our privacy policy has been developed to reflect Canadian and Ontario privacy laws and statutes.

For further information regarding Canadian and Ontario privacy laws, please visit:

  * [Office of the Information and Privacy Commissioner of Ontario](http://www.ipc.on.ca/)

**Advertising Networks**

Third-party vendors, including Google, use technology such as cookies and web beacons to serve ads based on your usage data.  Any information collected through this process is handled under the terms of our advertising partners' privacy policies. You can opt out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting <https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated>

**Google Analytics**

We use Google Analytics on some of our websites to collect information about usage. The information collected by Google Analytics will only be used for statistical analysis related to your browsing behaviour on this specific site. The information we obtain from Google Analytics is not personally identifying, nor is it combined with information from other sources to create personally identifying information.

Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit the site, but this cookie cannot be used by anyone except Google, and the data collected cannot be altered or retrieved by services from other domains.

Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](http://www.google.ca/analytics/terms/us.html) and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). You may choose to opt out by turning off cookies in the preferences settings in your web browser.

**Links to other web sites**

psiphontoday.com contains links to other websites of interest. Once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we have no control over any other website.  Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites, and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.
